Kheel, Theodore W. Legal Files 6021/004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- "How is He Doing After All?" - 6007-16 - Kheel v. Koch (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Contributors to Koch - 6007-18 - Kheel v. Koch (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Kheel v. Koch clippings (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Department of Investigation - 6007-20 - Kheel v. Koch (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Coalition for a Mayoral Choice - 6007-14 - Kheel v. Koch (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Board of Ethics correspondence - 6007-5 - Kheel v. Koch (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Reference cases - 6007-12 - Kheel v. Koch (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Kheel v. Koch - Amendments - New Yorkers for Koch fillings (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Supreme Court of State of New York, County of New York - Kheel v. Koch (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Reply brief on behalf of petitioners (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Kheel v. Koch - Brief on behalf of petitioners-appellants (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Pre-argument statement (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Hugh Carey correspondence - 6007-8 - Kheel v. Koch (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Notice of petition - 6007-9 - Kheel v. Koch (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Notice of settlement - 6007-11 - Kheel v. Koch (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Memo on opposition to petitioners' motion for leave to appeal (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Petitioners' memo of law - 6007-10 - Kheel v. Koch (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Correspondence and memos - 6007-1 - Kheel v. Koch (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous - 6007-4 - Kheel v. Koch (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Court papers-extra copies - 6007-3 - Kheel v. Koch (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Kheel v. Koch - Committee on Corruption (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Kheel v. Koch - Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Kheel v. Koch - Election and campaign financing materials (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Kheel cause materials - "Selected References on Strikes in America" (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Kheel Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 12)
- The Diebold Group Inc. - 6403-1 - Speeches and Articles, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Continuing Transportation Forum (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Norton Simon (Box 9, Folder 15)
- General Motors (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Highway Action Coalition (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Authority for Coordinating Transportation (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Freeman v. NBC, 1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Freeman v. NBC Correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Jacob Freeman v. NBC Orders, 1986-1988 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Freeman v. NBC Transcript of Hearing 4/24/87, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Freeman v. NBC Report & Recommendation 6/36/87, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Freeman v. NBC Report & Recommendation 9/18/87, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Freeman v. NBC Affidavit of Martin Ryan, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  Scope and Contents
  October 14, 1988
- Freeman v. NBC: Defendant's interrogation to certain plaintiffs, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Freeman v. NBC Transcript of Hearings 8/6/86, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Freeman v. NBC exhibits, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  9/23/86
- Freeman v. NBC Affidavit of Lawrence S. Lapidus, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  October 1986
- Freeman v. NBC Memorandum in Support of Motion for Stay, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  November 13, 1986
- Freeman v. NBC Memorandum Endorsement 7/31/89, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Freeman v. NBC Statement of Disputed Issues of Fact, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  November 8, 1988
- Freeman v. NBC Letters Retaining TWK, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  November 6, 1986
- Cristo - RE: 48 Howard Street (Freer Elevator Service Co.), 1986 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Cristo - Bibliography, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  March 11, 1987.
- Cristo - RE: Pont Newf (Paris Lawsuit), 1985 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  November 22, 1985
- Cristo: RE: 30 Downing Street, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Cristo- Miscellaneous, 1986-1988 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Cristo: Legal Fees 4/21/88, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Meyers, Catalina K, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Correspondence Marraccini, Francis and Nina and Conti Commodity Service, Inc. 6685-1, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  November 14, 1981.
- Briefs Marraccini, Francis and Nina and Conti Comodity Service, Inc 6695-2, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Drafts Marraccini, Francis and Nina and Conti Commodity Service, Inc. Arb. 6695-3, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Miscellaneous Marraccini, Francis and Nina and Conti Commodity Service, Inc. Arb. 6695-4 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Correspondence and Memos Karen Davis - Matter of Customs 6678-1, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Notes and Drafts Karen Davis - Matter of Customs 6678-2, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Client's Papers Karen Davis - Matter of Customs 6678-3, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  April 23, 1979.
- Miscellaneous Karen Davis - Matter of Customs 6678-4, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  August 22, 1979
- Petition for Relief Matter of Customs Karen Davis 6678-5, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  June 6, 1978.
- Karen Davis United States Court of International Trade Rules, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Correspondence and Memos Mascarotti 6681-1, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  March 2. 1979
- Miscellaneous Mascarotti 6681-2, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  Employment Agreement
- Correspondence & Memos Civil Service Employees Association & Public Employment Relations Board 6660-1, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  October 17, 1977
- Drafts Civil Service Employees Association & Public Employment Relations Board 6660-2, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  March 8, 1977
- News Paper Clippings Civil Service Employees Association & Public Employment Relation Board 6660-3, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  January 21, 1977
- Record Binder CSEA 6660-4, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Correspondence & Memos Sensormatic 6065-1, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  September 17, 1983
- Hearing Sensormatic 6065-3, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  February 7, 1983
- Union Contract Sensormatic 6065-5, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  June 14, 1978
- Drafts & Copies Sensormatic 6065-7, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  June 13, 1978
- Correspondence & Memos Treesdale, Inc. 6694-1, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  December 31, 1982
- Corporate & Minutes Treesdale, Inc. 6694-2, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  November 6, 1981
- Miscellaneous Treesdale, Inc. 6694-3, 1971-1978 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Questionnaires Treesdale, Inc., 1978 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  December 31, 1978
- Financials Treesdale, Inc. 6694-5, 1971-1975 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  November 1971 - February 1975
- TWK Treesdale, Inc. Current, 1971-1975 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  August 26, 1971 - February 10, 1975
- Correspondence Comstraw vs. UDC 6688-1, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  7/13/78 - 10/29/79
- Court Papers Comstraw vs. UDC 6688-2, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Welcome Wagon International Correspondence 90-1, 1965-1970 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  11/19/65 - 1/19/70
- Welcome Wagon International Agreements and Drafts of Agreement 90-3, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  2/36/1965
- Welcome Wagon International Legal Papers 90-5, 1949-1951 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  9/24/1949 - 1/10/1951
- Welcome Wagon International Miscellaneous 90-6, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  11/24/1965
- NYC - Labor Employment Standards, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Entenmann's Bakery, Inc. 94-10, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Entenmann's Bakery, Inc. Motion Papes 94-9, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Entenmann's Bakery, Inc. Memorandum of Law 94-8, 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Entenmann's Bakery, Inc. Interrogatories 94-6, 1965-1968 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Entenmann's Bakery, Inc. Stipulations 94-5, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Correspondence & Memos Heritage Knitwear, Inc. 6013-1, 1979-1982 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Agreements Heritage Knitwear, Inc. 6013-2, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Financials Heritage Knitwear, Inc. 6013-3, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Escrow Papers Heritage Knitwear, Inc. 6013-4, 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Corporate Papers Heritage Knitwear, Inc. 6013-5, 1978-1980 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Memoranda & Law 141 E. 55th. Vs. Orfil 06011.001-2, 1969-1985 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Court Papers - X Copies 141 E. 55th vs. Orfil 06011.001, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Court Papers - Originals 141 E. 55th vs. Orfil 06011.002-5, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Drafts 141 E. 55th vs. Orfil 06011.001-6, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Miscellaneous 141 E. 55th vs. Orfil 06011.001-7, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Client's Papers 141 E. 55th vs. Orfil 06011.001-8, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Correspondence & Memos " 21" Club, Inc. 6008-1, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  12/8/82-10/21/83
- Drafts " 21" Club, Inc. 6008-2, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Letter of Intent " 21" Club, Inc. 6008-3, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Financials " 21" Club, Inc. 6008-4, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Correspondence Theodore Kheel vs. Republic National Bank 6010-1, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Background Material Theodore W. Kheel vs. Republic National Bank 6010-2, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Correspondence Western Union Telegraph Company 6346-1, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Corporate Papers Re: W U T, Co. 6346-2, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Minutes from January 1971 W U T, Co. 6346-3 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Western Union Telegraph Co. 6346-3 Minutes 5/1969-11/24/70, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Annual Meeting of Stockholders W U T Co., 1982 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Duplicates and Drafts Western Union Telegraph Company 6346-5, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous Western Union Telegraph Company 6346-6, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Questionnaires W U T, INC 6346-9, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Prospecti 6346-10, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Post Effective Amendment #2 6346-11 WUT Co, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Form S-1 6346-12, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Advs. Ruth S. Kleinman Western Union Telegraph Co. 6346-13, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Advs. Martha Price Western Union Telegraph Co. 6146-14, 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Western Union Ranch Western Union Telegraph Co. 6346-15, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Curtiss-Wright Corporation Western Union 6346-16, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Acquisition of E.F. Johnson Co. Western Union Telegraph Co. 6346-17, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Administrative Tribunal Judgment No. 236 Case No. 225 Belchamber 6670-4.1.8 10/20/78, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Labor Letters Bakers Home Service 6460, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  April 20, 1956
- Labor Letter #1 6460, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  September 19, 1955
- Labor Letter #2 6460, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  October 20, 1955
- Labor Letter #3 J.W.K. and R.E.H. 6460, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  November 17, 1955
- Labor Letter #4 J.W.K. and R.E.H. 6460, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  December 20, 1955
- Labor Letter #4 (Supplement) T.W.K. and R.E.H. 6460, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Labor Letter #5 T.W.K. and R.E.H. 6460, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  January 18, 1956
- Labor Letter #6 J.W.K. and R.E.H. 6460, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  2-17-56
- Labor Letter #7 6460, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  March 16, 1956
- Labor Letter #8 6460, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  April 18, 1956
- Labor Letter #9 6460, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  5-21-56
- Labor Letter #10 6460, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  6-20-56
- Abbatiello vs. Gelfo Manufacturing Co., Inc. Athlone Industries, Inc. 6074.10, 1978-1981 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Francis Kutt - Unfair Labor Practice Charge Dudley Sport Co. Div. 6074.1, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Abbitstion-Lourdes Travino Bimbi Shoe Co., 6074.3, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Representation Dudley Sport Co., Div. 6074.2, 1973-1977 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Tami Sportswear - Union Agreement Athlone Industries, Inc. 6074.4, 1973-1975 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Darius, Inc. Athlone Industries - Labor Mattes 6047.5, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Anna Edmonds Re: Labor Matters Athlone Inc. 6074.6, 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Aristocrat Apparel Labor Matters Athlone Industries, Inc. 6074.7, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- William Homan vs. Reynold Fastener Athlone Industries - Labor Matters 6074.9, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Piscitelli vs. Gelfo Athlone Industries, Inc. 6074.11, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Byron Clinton vs. Reynolds Fasteners Re: Labor Matters Athlone Industries, Inc., 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Path Trans Fare Increase, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- World Trade Center Kheel, T.W. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  1961
- Transportation Bond Issue Kheel, T.W., 1973 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- National Labor Relations Board, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Authority for Coordinating Transportation, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Removing Obstacles to Automation 6426, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Round Table Meeting on Wage Stabilization, 1944 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  February 18, 1944
- Hackey v. NFL Defendants' Post-Trial Memorandum (with Appendix), 1975 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  September 5, 1975